Guide to the Office of the Dean of the College of Arts and Science (Santirocco) RG.19.0.4
New York University Archives
Records of the Office of the Dean of the College of Arts and Science (Santirocco)
1992-2014
New York University Archives
New York University. College of Arts and Science. Office of the Dean
RG.19.0.4
0.88 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes
The College of Arts and Science is the founding school of New York University. It is NYU's largest academic unit, comprising the College of Arts and Science, the Graduate School of Arts and Science, and Liberal Studies. The Arts and Science faculty are global scholars within the academic divisions of Science, Social Sciences and Humanities. They teach across the Arts and Science community and NYU, through dozens of departments, research centers, institutes, and international houses. Dr. Matthew S. Santirocco is Professor of Classics and Angelo J. Ranieri Director of Ancient Studies at New York University; he also serves as Faculty Director of NYU-Washington, DC. From 2011-2017 he was Senior Vice Provost for Academic Affairs, and from 1994-2011 he served as the Seryl Kushner Dean of the College of Arts and Science at NYU. As of April 2025, he is the Interim Seryl Kushner Dean of the College of Arts and Science. The Records of the Office of the Dean of the College of Arts and Science (Santirocco) (1992-2014) consists of programs, speeches, and signage for the annual Dean's Awards Ceremony. Also included is the script for the 1992 College of Arts and Science Class Night.
Scope and Contents
The Records of the Office of the Dean of the College of Arts and Science (Santirocco) (1992-2014) consists of programs, speeches, and signage for the annual Dean's Awards Ceremony. Also included is the script for the 1992 College of Arts and Science Class Night.
Historical Note
The College of Arts and Science is the founding school of New York University. It is NYU's largest academic unit, comprising the College of Arts and Science, the Graduate School of Arts and Science, and Liberal Studies. The Arts and Science faculty are global scholars within the academic divisions of Science, Social Sciences and Humanities. They teach across the Arts and Science community and NYU, through dozens of departments, research centers, institutes, and international houses.
Dr. Matthew S. Santirocco is Professor of Classics and Angelo J. Ranieri Director of Ancient Studies at New York University; he also serves as Faculty Director of NYU-Washington, DC. From 2011-2017 he was Senior Vice Provost for Academic Affairs, and from 1994-2011 he served as the Seryl Kushner Dean of the College of Arts and Science at NYU. As of April 2025, he is the Interim Seryl Kushner Dean of the College of Arts and Science.
Arrangement
Arranged in chronological order.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by Reese Buckholz, Program Administrator, CAS Honors Program in April 2025. The accession number associated with this transfer is 2025.017.
Education, Higher -- Awards; Award dinners; Speeches, addresses, etc.; Programs (documents); New York University. College of Arts and Science. Office of the Dean
- College of Arts and Science Class Night Script, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Signage, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script, Signage, and Program, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Dean's Award Ceremony -- Script and Program, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 10)